Finding Aid for the Ralph Edwards Productions Production Records PASC.0336
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Truth or Consequences, 1940-1988; Series 2.
  - Scripts and Production Materials, Subseries 1.
    - Season 13, Program no. 819 (Script), 1952 June 17; script (Box 13)
      Taped on June 6, 1952 for NBC in Hollywood, Ca. Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk.
      1st show for Pet Milk and 1st show of 13th season. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 13, Program no. 820 (Script), 1952 June 24; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk.
      Live performance radio broadcast from New York City on NBC.
    - Season 13, Program no. 821, 1952 July 1; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Celebrity guest(s): Rock Hudson.
      Taped on June 13, 1952 in Hollywood, CA for NBC. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 13, Program no. 822, 1952 July 15; script (Box 13)
      Taped on June 20, 1952 in Chicago, IL for NBC. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 13, Program no. 823, 1952 July 29; script (Box 13)
      Taped on June 27, 1952 in Chicago, IL for NBC. For radio broadcast.
    - Season 13, Program no. 824, 1952 August 5; script (Box 13)
      Taped on June 17, 1952 in San Francisco, CA for NBC. For radio broadcast.
    - Season 13, Program no. 825, 1952 August 12; script (Box 13)
      Performed live in Hollywood, CA for NBC. For radio broadcast.
    - Season 13, Program no. 826, 1952 August 19; script (Box 13)
      Taped on June 30, 1952 in Hollywood, CA for NBC. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 13, Program no. 827, 1952 August 26; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Celebrity guest(s): Groucho Marx.
      Performed live in Hollywood, CA for NBC. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 13, Program no. 828, 1952 September 2; script (Box 13)
    - Season 13, Program no. 829, 1952 September 9; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Celebrity guest(s): Champ Butler.
    - Season 13, Program no. 830, 1952 September 18; script (Box 13)
    - Season 13, Program no. 831, 1952 September 18; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Celebrity guest(s): Susan Cabot.
      Taped on September 23, 1952 at Camp Pendelton, CA for NBC. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 13, Program no. 832, 1952 October 2; script (Box 13)
    - Season 13, Program no. 833, 1952 October 9; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Celebrity guest: Dana Andrews.
    - Season 13, Program no. 834, 1952 October 16; script (Box 13)
      Performed live in Hollywood, CA for NBC. Mystery authors JAMES M. FOX, DOROTHY B. HUGHES, JONATHAN LATTIMER & STEWART PALMER. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 13, Program no. 835, 1952 October 23; script (Box 13)
    - Season 13, Program no. 836, 1952 October 23; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Celebrity guest: Jerry Gray (singer).
    - Season 13, Program no. 837, 1952 November 6; script (Box 13)
    - Season 13, Program no. 838, 1952 November 13; script (Box 13)
    - Season 13, Program no. 839, 1952 November 20; script (Box 13)
    - Season 13, Program no. 840, 1952 November 27; script (Box 13)
    - Season 13, Program no. 841, 1952 December 4; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Celebrity guest: Virginia Mayo.
    - Season 13, Program no. 842, 1952 December 11; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Debut of unidentified Gordon MacRae song.
    - Season 13, Program no. 843, 1952 December 18; script (Box 13)
    - Season 13, Program no. 844, 1952 December 25; script (Box 13)
      Performed live(?) in Hollywood, CA for NBC. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 13, Program no. 845, 1953 January 1; script (Box 13)
    - Season 13, Program no. 846, 1953 January 8; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Celebrity guest: Gisele MacKenzie.
    - Season 13, Program no. 847, 1953 January 15; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: TALL STORY CARRYOVER #3 > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: TELEPHONE CONTEST WINNER, HIGH SCHOOL ANNUAL > ELEPHANT FABLE
    - Season 13, Program no. 848, 1953 January 22; script (Box 13)
    - Program nos. 849-929 (Scripts), 1960 April 20-August 10 (Box 33)
    - Season 13, Program no. 849, 1953 January 29; script (Box 13)
    - Season 13, Program no. 850, 1953 February 5; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Celebrity guest: Broderick Crawford.
    - Season 13, Program no. 851, 1953 February 12; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Celebrity guest: Margaret Whiting.
    - Season 13, Program no. 852, 1953 February 19; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: AMATEUR SONG WRITER (contestant: Bob Hilton) (celebrities: Smith, Jack; Stabile, Dick; Flanagan, Ralph )> SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: RETURN WATCH, WHEEL CHAIR PHONE > HONORARY MAYOR MENTION > RIDE CHIEF
      Performed live in Hollywood, CA for NBC. Plug Flanagan at Hollywood Palladium; Stabile was arranger & conductor for Dean Martin & Jerry Lewis TV show. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 13, Program no. 853, 1953 February 26; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: ROSEMARY CLOONEY > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: LAST FLING, FLY SOLDIER HOME, HONORARY MAYOR MENTION > GENERAL GEORGE C. KENNY
    - Season 13, Program no. 854, 1953 March 5; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: SCOTCH KILTS WATER TANK > RIPE OLIVE TUNA RING CARRYOVER BUILDUP > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: RETURN RING, LOST FATHER REUNION > HONORARY T OR C MAYOR
    - Season 13, Program no. 855, 1953 March 12; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: STARS MOTHERS > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: HEARING AID, FALSE TEETH, REPAIRED CAR > HONORARY MAYOR MENTION > RIPE OLIVE TUNA RING CARRYOVER PAYOFF
      Performed live in Hollywood, CA for NBC. MOMS OF GARY COOPER, DOROTHY LAMOUR, LOU COSTELLO, DEAN MARTIN, JOAN CRAWFORD, SCOTTY BECKETT, FRED MacMURRAY, RONALD REAGAN, DONALD O'CONNOR, RICHARD CARLSON, JOHN HOWARD, PENNY SINGLETON, ROBERT PAGE, EDDIE ALBERT, BONITA GRANVILLE. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 13, Program no. 856, 1953 March 19; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: BATHING SUITS PACKAGE > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: PILLOW CASE, HONOR STUDENT > SKUNK HITCHHIKE CARRYOVER #1 (contestant: Harold Tucker) BUILDUP (NYC REMOTE)
    - Season 13, Program no. 857, 1953 March 26; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: TAXI VACATION > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: STOLEN WATCH, ORPHAN'S CIRCUS > HONORARY MAYOR WINNER > SKUNK HITCHHIKE CARRYOVER #2 (conestant: Harold Tucker)
    - Season 13, Program no. 858, 1953 April 2; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: SWAMI - HUSBAND > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: BOY - DOG REUNION, BEAUTY CONTEST > ST. LOUIS BROWNS > SKUNK HITCHHIKE CARRYOVER #3 (contestant: Harold Tucker).
      Taped March 1, 1953 in Hollywood, CA for NBC. St. Louis Browns: Vic Wertz (?), Dick Kryhoski, Babe Martin, Bob Habenicht, Hal White, Ed Mickelson, Virgil Trucks, Duane Pillette, Dixie Upright, (?), Don Masterson (?), Bob Young, Art Peters, Frank Kellert, Bob Cain. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 13, Program no. 859, 1953 April 9; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: MYSTERY MAN PAYOFF (contestant and winner: Bill Perry)> MAN'S GIFTS (contestant: Mrs. Jean Little)> SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: GOVERNOR MECHEM, CITY HALL SIGN, HONORARY MAYOR (contestant: Lynne Higinbotham), CHURCH ESSAY (contestant: Mary Faye Leign)(celebrity: Jimmy Stewart), OLD FIDDLER'S CONTEST (contestant: Suzie Snodgrass)> SKUNK HITCHHIKE CARRYOVER #4 PAYOFF (contestant: Harold Tucker)
      Taped April 4, 1953 in Truth or Consequences, NM for NBC. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 13, Program no. 860, 1953 April 16; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: IMPEDIMENT DRAMA > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: TELEPHONE - CANARY, LETTER AWARD, SAILOR'S WALLET > HUSBAND - MERMAID WATER TANK (contestants: Mr. & Mrs. Robert Harding)
      Broadcast from Hollywood, CA for NBC. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 13, Program no. 861, 1953 April 23; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: OPERA STAR (contestant: Jack Petty) > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: GOLD FOOTBALL, G.I. REUNION > HYPNOTIST WIFE
    - Season 13, Program no. 862, 1953 April 30; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: LOUSE UP CONTESTANT > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: AIRMAN WAAF REUNION, VARIETY CLUB (aka BOBBY RIGGIO #2 - ALAN SANDERS) > STAR (EDMUND O'BRIEN)
      Broadcast from Las Vegas, NV (Flamingo Hotel) for NBC. SURPRISE CONSEQUENCE (R.E. in audience) - go up on stage with R.E. - gets phonograph - sings "OVER THE RAINBOW" - request contributions in his name; if $5000 donated we give $500 Savings Bond - TV set, freezer & folding wheelchair to school. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 13, Program no. 863, 1953 May 7; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: PLANT WALLET > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: BOY - DOG - PHONE, FRATERNITY RING, PET MILK PHONE NUMBER > VARIETY CLUB MENTION > WHAT'S MY NAME SELTZER
    - Season 13, Program no. 864, 1953 May 14; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: AD LIB DRAMA (RHONDA FLEMING) > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: PHONE - GIRL - FRIEND (contestant: Cpl. James Burton) - BAND, EL TORO SERVICE > CROSS COUNTRY BICYCLE CARRYOVER #1 BUILDUP (contestants: Marine Cpl. Don Mainland and Sgt. Sam Scherr).
      Taped May 11, 1953 in El Toro Marine Base (Santa Ana, CA) for NBC. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 13, Program no. 865, 1953 May 21; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: RIP OWN HAT > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: FRATERNITY PINS, LIBERACE - GIRL SINGER > CROSS COUNTRY BICYCLE CARRYOVER #2 (contestants: Marine Cpl. Don Mainland, Sgt. Sam Scherr).
    - Season 13, Program no. 866, 1953 May 28; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: FILIBUSTER > GEORGE MONTGOMERY > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: LOST LOCKET, LOST WEDDING BOOK > CROSS COUNTRY BICYCLE CARRYOVER #3 (contestants: Marine Cpl. Don Mainland, Sgt. Sam Scherr).
    - Season 13, Program no. 867, 1953 June 4; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: CIGARETTE LIGHTER > FOREIGN COMMERCIALS > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: RETURN WEDDING RING, SINGING CALLICOATS > CROSS COUNTRY BICYCLE CARRYOVER #4 (contestants: Marine Cpl. Don Mainland, Sgt. Sam Scherr). PAYOFF
    - Season 13, Program no. 868, 1953 June 11; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: MEMORY TEST FRAME > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: BASS VIOL RETURN, TEXAS MOTHER SON REUNION > LOVE COUNT
    - Season 14, Program no. 869, 1953 June 18; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: TIME CHANGE RUNNING GAG BUILDUP > HAYES & HEALY (Peter Hayes, Mary Healy) > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: DOG SUMMONS > TIME CHANGE RUNNING GAG (contestant: Mrs. Ruth Polisner) PAYOFF
    - Season 14, Program no. 870, 1953 June 24; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: WIFE VS. MODEL > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: OVERSEAS DUTY, DISGUISE WIFE SECRETARY > APPLE OVER SOLDIER
      Taped on June 19, 1953 from Fort MacArthur (San Pedro, CA - BASE) for NBC. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 14, Program no. 871, 1953 July 1; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: MARBLE CAKE > TELEPHONE FAMILY RACE > GOODWILL GIFTS > HUSBAND VS. EDWARDS
      Taped on June 23,1953 from Occidental College (Eagle Rock, Los Angeles, CA) for NBC. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 14, Program no. 872, 1953 July 8; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: MAYOR'S WIFE > COACH CHORUS > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: PAPER BOY VACATION > FIRE CHIEF HOTFOOT
      Taped on June 12,1953 (?) from Oakland, CA (Municipal Theatre) for NBC. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 14, Program no. 873, 1953 July 15; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: FRENCH QUESTION (Celebrity: Joan Vohz)> T OR C DIXIELAND BAND > MIXED UP WIVES > ADVISE COLONEL
      Taped on June 12,1953 (?) from Camp Stoneman (Oakland, CA - ARMY BASE)for NBC. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 14, Program no. 874, 1953 July 22; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: STAR OBSERVATION TEST (celebrity: Joan Weldon)> SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: SEA BAG, MIND READER TELEPHONE > IDENTIFY TEN OBJECTS
      Taped on June 13,1953 (?) from U.S. Naval Station, Treasure Island (San Francisco, CA - BASE) for NBC. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 14, Program no. 875, 1953 July 29; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: $20 SOX > WHISTLE DIXIE > SING GROCERY LIST > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: PLUG STORE, PRISONER SONG (Pamela Britton)> ITALIAN COW
      Taped on June 13,1953 (?) from San Francisco, CA for NBC. PAMELA BRITTON (GUYS & DOLLS ref) sings "CAFE LA RUE" by convict "ANDY" (Virgil Anderson); San Quentin Warden HARLEY TEETS. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 14, Program no. 876, 1953 August 5; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: OBEY HUSBAND MIKE > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: FRED BEAVER, DRESSMAKER DAUGHTER REUNION > (PRIZE SONG)
      Taped on July 31,1953 from Hollywood, CA for NBC. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 14, Program no. 877, 1953 August 12; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: ENGLISH LESSON LOVE (celebrity: Rod Cameron)> SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: VALENTINO, POLIO HONEYMOON > MILLSTREAM SING - TALK
    - Season 14, Program no. 878, 1953 August 19; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: FROZEN PINEAPPLE DESSERT CARRYOVER BUILDUP (RUNNING GAG) (contestant: Miss Glad Dunn) > EXPLAIN BASEBALL (BOB KELLY, announcer for L.A. Angels of the Pacific Coast League (his part scripted)) > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: ORPHANAGE FREEZER, MOTHERS-IN-LAW WAR BRIDE
    - Season 14, Program no. 879, 1953 August 26; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: DOUBLE DATE TELEPHONE > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: CONNIE HAINES, MAJOR REUNION > FROZEN PINEAPPLE DESSERT CARRYOVER (contestant: Miss Glad Dunn) PAYOFF
      Broadcast live from Hollywood, CA for NBC. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 14, Program no. 880, 1953 September 2; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: MOTHER-IN-LAW GOAT > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: 200 YEAR OLD SPOON, MOTHERS-IN-LAW WEDDING
      Recorded August 19, 1953 from Hollywood, CA for NBC. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 14, Program no. 881, 1953 September 9; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: VENTRILOQUIST DUMMY HUSBAND > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: FOUR PRIZES, HOTEL WORKER'S VACATION > SPEECH SONG JOKE
    - Season 14, Program no. 882, 1953 September 16; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Ken Carpenter. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: JACK SMITH IMITATORS > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: MISSED GOOD GESTURE, RETURN EDITOR'S DESK
    - Season 14, Program no. 883, 1953 September 24; script (Box 13)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Harlow Wilcox. Sponsor: Pet Milk. Acts: SQUIRT HUGH > SURPRISE CONSEQUENCES: HELP OLD LADY, FRYRYTE CONTEST WINNERS (MR. & MRS. PERRY E. THOMPSON won trip to PARIS)> BRAG ON SELF
      Taped on September 23, 1953 from Hollywood, CA for NBC. Radio broadcast.
    - Season 14, Program nos. 884-911, 1953 October 1-1954 April 8 (Box 22)
      Host: Ralph Edwards. Announcer: Harlow Wilcox. Network: NBC. Sponsor: Pet Milk.
    - Program nos. 918-1035, 1971 April 7-1971 December 30; scripts (Box 246)
    - Program nos. 930-976 (Scripts), 1960 August 15-October 14 (Box 35)
    - Program nos. 977-1058 (Scripts), 1960 October 17-1961 January 24 (Box 1)
      Host: Bob Barker
    - Program nos. 1036-1063, 1971 December 31-1972 February 17; scripts (Box 249)
    - Program no. 1059 (Master Script and Research), 1961 January 27 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Sponsor: Heinz; Proctor & Gamble. Acts: SINGING CONTEST SURPRISE BUILDUP & PAYOFF > DRIVE IN STAR QUESTIONS BUILDUP & PAYOFF Celebrity Guest: Jeff Chandler.
      Air date: 2/16/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1060 (Master Script and Research), 1961 January 30 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Sponsors: Alberto-Culver; American Home. Acts: WRONG SEAT DRIVER FRAME > WHAT YEAR CELEBRITIES BUILDUP (Wykoff, Frank; Bundy, May Sutton; Bushman, Francis X.) & PAYOFF
      Air date: 2/17/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1061 (Master Script and Research), 1961 January 30 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Sponsors: Miles; Procter & Gamble. Acts: MOTHER GOOSE TRANSLATIONS > STRONGBOX CARRYOVER > STAGE DOOR JOHNNY REUNION BUILDUP & PAYOFF
      Air date: 2/20/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1062 (Master Script and Research), 1961 January 31 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Sponsors: Beechnut; Nabisco; Alberto-Culver. Acts: DISCOVER STAR TEACHER REMOTE BUILDUP (Celebrities: Milner, Martin; Maharis, George) > BLINDFOLD GIFT BUYERS > DISCOVER STAR TEACHER REMOTE RECAP & PAYOFF
      Air date: 2/21/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1063 (Master Script and Research), 1961 January 31 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Sponsors: Heinz; Procter & Gamble. Acts: SOUND OFF MOTHER-IN-LAW REUNION > STRONGBOX CARRYOVER > ROWAN & MARTIN MOVIES BUILDUP (celebrities: Rowan, Dan; Martin, Dick) & PAYOFF
      Air date: 2/22/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1064 (Master Script and Research), 1961 February 3 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Sponsors: Jergens; Proctor & Gamble. Acts: WIVES TIME BUYERS BUILDUP > INSULTING WARDROBE FRAME > OBSERVE $100 HEADLINE > WIVES TIME BUYERS PAYOFF
      Air date: 2/23/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program nos. 1064-1179, 1971 February 18-1972 June 14; scripts (Box 248)
    - Program no. 1065 (Master Script and Research), 1961 February 3 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Sponsors: Frigidaire; American Home; Proctor & Gamble. Acts: RAG PICTURE GIFTS BUILDUP & PAYOFF > BABY BROTHER COMPLAINTS BUILDUP & PAYOFF
      Air date: 2/24/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1066 (Master Script and Research), 1961 February 20 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Sponsors: Frigidaire; Proctor & Gamble. Acts: PICK WIFE SIZE WARDROBE > STRONGBOX CARRYOVER > BALLET EMOTIONS BUILDUP & PAYOFF
      Air date: 2/27/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1067 (Master Script and Research), 1961 February 20 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Sponsors: Nabisco; Jergens; Miles. Acts: PAY PHONE JACKPOT > MAKE LIST - MAKE STORY > SING ANSWERS INTERVIEW > CHANGE $5 BILL
      Air date: 2/28/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1068 (Master Script and Research), 1961 February 21 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Sponsors: Beechnut; Proctor & Gamble. Acts: DEFENDANT BARKER BUILDUP & PAYOFF > BLONDE BRUNETTE SERGEANT SURPRISE BUILDUP & PAYOFF
      Air date: 3/1/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1069 (Master Script and Research), 1961 January 16 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Sponsors: Heinz; Proctor & Gamble. Acts: HUBBY LADY HAT BUYERS BUILDUP & PAYOFF > STAR COMPARISON HUSBAND BUILDUP (celebrity: Rory Calhoun) & PAYOFF
      Air date: 3/2/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1070 (Master Script and Research), 1961 February 21 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Sponsors: Alberto-Culver; American Home; Beechnut. Acts: SELECT BELLRINGERS BUILDUP & PAYOFF > MIND MATCHERS CONTEST TEASE #1 > FIND KIDS WISHES BUILDUP & PAYOFF
      Air date: 3/3/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1071 (Master Script and Research), 1961 February 22 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Sponsors: Miles; Procter & Gamble. Acts: KOOKIE KAR SALESLADY REUNION BUILDUP > DRAG HUBBY SINGER > MIND MATCHERS CONTEST TEASE #2 > STRONGBOX CARRYOVER > KOOKIE KAR SALESLADY REUNION PAYOFF
      Air date: 3/6/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1072 (Master Script and Research), 1961 February 22 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Sponsors: Beechnut; Nabisco; Alberto-Culver. Acts: YES OR NO PEOPLE BETTORS BUILDUP & PAYOFF > FIND WIVES AUDIENCE BUILDUP & PAYOFF
      Air date: 3/7/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1073 (Master Script and Research), 1961 March 2 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Sponsors: Heinz; Procter & Gamble. Acts: BET ON SIMPLE TASKS BUILDUP & PAYOFF > MIND MATCHERS CONTEST TEASE #3 > MATCH AUTOBIOGRAPHY LADIES BUILDUP & PAYOFF
      Air date: 3/8/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1074 (Master Script and Research), 1961 March 6 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Acts: DESCRIBE FASHIONS SURPRISE > STRONGBOX CARRYOVER > PLACE PERFORMERS BUILDUP & PAYOFF
      Air date: 3/9/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1075 (Master Script and Research), 1961 March 6 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Acts: CUT TIE DOUBLE FRAME BUILDUP & PAYOFF > MIND MATCHERS CONTEST TEASE #4 > PENNY MACHINE PREDICTORS BUILDUP & PAYOFF
      Air date: 3/10/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1076 (Master Script and Research), 1961 February 27 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Acts: PRINCIPAL BOBBO BUILDUP & PAYOFF > HAFF BROTHERS TRIO BUILDUP & PAYOFF
      Air date: 3/13/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1077 (Master Script and Research), 1961 February 27 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Acts: BARKER SAYS BUILDUP & PAYOFF > MIND MATCHERS CONTEST TEASE #5 > ACADEMY AWARD SONGS BUILDUP & PAYOFF
      Air date: 3/14/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1078 (Master Script and Research), 1961 February 28 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Acts: SANDPILE GIFTS REMOTE BUILDUP > GUESS COMIC STRIP CHARACTERS > SANDPILE GIFTS REMOTE CUT-IN > COMPLIMENTARY CLOCKS > SANDPILE GIFTS REMOTE PAYOFF
      Air date: 3/15/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1079 (Master Script and Research), 1961 February 28 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Acts: WHEEL OF FORTUNE HUBBIES > STRONGBOX CARRYOVER > MIND MATCHERS CONTEST TEASE #6 > MERRY GO ROUND REUNION BUILDUP & PAYOFF
      Air date: 3/16/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1080 (Master Script and Research), 1961 March 2 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Acts: OBSTACLE TRICYCLE GIFTS > $100 POKER FACES > MADISON AVENUE ANDREWS BUILDUP (celebrity: Dana Andrews) & PAYOFF
      Air date: 3/17/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1081 (Master Script and Research), 1961 March 7 (Box 2)
      Host: Bob Barker. Acts: GREEDY WIVES FRAME > STRONGBOX CARRYOVER > MIND MATCHERS CONTEST TEASE #7 > VOICE THROWER HALLWAY BUILDUP & PAYOFF
      Air date: 3/20/1961. Television broadcast.
    - Program no. 1082 (Master Script and Research), 1961 March 7 (Box 2)